<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on Beards, Bytes and Brews</title>
    <link>https://www.dantuck.com/article/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on Beards, Bytes and Brews</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 10:30:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.dantuck.com/article/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pass extension: Safe</title>
      <link>https://www.dantuck.com/article/pass-extension-safe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 10:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dantuck.com/article/pass-extension-safe/</guid>
      <description>Pass is becoming my goto for password management. It is a very easy to use manager and has a great list of extensions as well as the ability to create your own extensions. I have found that I need to solve a very specific problem where I need a printed backup of all data that is stored in the password store.
The Problem Pass is pretty cool and offers a lot of options to store passwords and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rclone - rsync for cloud storage</title>
      <link>https://www.dantuck.com/article/rclone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dantuck.com/article/rclone/</guid>
      <description>Rclone is a really cool command line tool that can sync files and directories too and from many sources. A full list of sources can be found on their official website.
I personally use it for syncing local backups to Backblaze B2.
Installation There are a few ways to install but I prefer the script install:
To install rclone on Linux/macOS/BSD systems, run:
$ curl https://rclone.org/install.sh | sudo bash  Configuration The easiest way to configure and get up and running is by:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GnuPG and Pass</title>
      <link>https://www.dantuck.com/article/gnupg-and-pass/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 06:10:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dantuck.com/article/gnupg-and-pass/</guid>
      <description>I find myself constantly referring to different sources to setup my password manager; Pass. This reference is going to provide a source for reference that includes both.
Installation References (Archlinux)
 https://wiki.archlinux.org/index.php/Pass https://wiki.archlinux.org/index.php/GnuPG  GnuGP According to the official website:
GnuPG is a complete and free implementation of the OpenPGP standard as defined by RFC4880 (also known as PGP). GnuPG allows you to encrypt and sign your data and communications; it features a versatile key management system, along with access modules for all kinds of public key directories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Verizon Pixel and Pixel XL Bootloader Unlock</title>
      <link>https://www.dantuck.com/article/verizon-pixel-and-pixel-xl-bootloader-unlock/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dantuck.com/article/verizon-pixel-and-pixel-xl-bootloader-unlock/</guid>
      <description>As all Pixel owners should know by now there is a end of support scheduled for each phone they ship. I like many others have a perfectly functional Pixel device which will soon be vulnerable to security issues and without Google support I am left with little options. I am not one to need the latest and greatest so I have chosen to install LineageOS.
The greatest problem with Verizon is that they prevent you from toggling the &amp;ldquo;OEM unlocking&amp;rdquo; which would allow you to wipe the device then sideload a new OS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual Studio Code - Selected Text to Uppercase</title>
      <link>https://www.dantuck.com/article/visual-studio-code-selected-text-to-uppercase/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 12:58:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dantuck.com/article/visual-studio-code-selected-text-to-uppercase/</guid>
      <description>In Visual Studio we are all used to being able to use CTRL+SHIFT+U to transform the selected text to uppercase but for Visual Studio Code this key binding was left out. As long as you are using Version 1.8.1 or above you will be able to take advantage of the built in keyboard shortcuts. Do the following to enable the keybindings.
Note: Ubuntu users will need to use a modified binding; change to ctrl+alt+u and ctrl+alt+l.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raspberry Pi: Fixing your Locale</title>
      <link>https://www.dantuck.com/article/raspberry-pi-simple-nas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 12:02:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dantuck.com/article/raspberry-pi-simple-nas/</guid>
      <description>Fixing your Locale on Raspberry Pi After a fresh install of Raspbian you will likely see the following error:
bash: warning: setlocale: LC_ALL: cannot change locale (en_US.UTF-8)  You can fix your locale with a few simple updates.
 Edit /etc/locale.gen and uncomment the line with en_US.UTF-8 Run locale-gen en_US.UTF-8 Run update-locale en_US.UTF-8  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>